https://tradewins.com/privacy-policy

Customer Satisfaction Survey 2020
My Cart: 0 Items ($0.00)
Keith Harwood
Kerry Given (Dr. Duke)
Keith Harwood
Kerry Given (Dr. Duke)
TradeWins Publishing Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to us. This policy explains how TradeWins Publishing treats Personal Information that TradeWins Publishing collects and receives, including Personal Information related to your use of TradeWins Publishing services. This policy applies to all Personal Information collected or submitted on the TradeWins Publishing site. The term “Personal Information” means information about an individual that is personally identifiable and not publicly available, such as one's name, contact details and credit card information.
Collection of Personal Information
You may choose to provide us with Personal Information through this website. Such information, including your name, email address, zip code and other personal information, may be requested when you register with TradeWins Publishing, use TradeWins Publishing services or visit the website(s) of TradeWins Publishing or its affiliates, advertisers, sponsors or other business partners. To subscribe to TradeWins Publishing services and complete transactions through TradeWins Publishing, you must provide additional Personal Information for billing purposes, including credit card or other billing and payment information.
If you choose not to provide requested Personal Information, you will not be able to register with TradeWins Publishing services, subscribe to TradeWins Publishing services, make any purchases or other transactions, obtain certain services or receive certain benefits that require such disclosure. TradeWins Publishing is the sole owner of all Personal Information provided to it.
Definitions
Service
Service any service provided by TradeWins Publishing or TradeWins.com
Personal Data
Personal Data means data about a living individual who can be identified from those data (or from those and other information either in our possession or likely to come into our possession).
Usage Data
Usage Data is data collected automatically either generated by the use of the Service or from the Service infrastructure itself (for example, the duration of a page visit).
Cookies
Cookies are small pieces of data stored on your device (computer or mobile device).
Data Controller
Data Controller means the natural or legal person who (either alone or jointly or in common with other persons) determines the purposes for which and the manner in which any personal information are, or are to be, processed.
For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, we are a Data Controller of your Personal Data.
Data Processors (or Service Providers)
Data Processor (or Service Provider) means any natural or legal person who processes the data on behalf of the Data Controller.
We may use the services of various Service Providers in order to process your data more effectively.
Data Subject (or User)
Data Subject is any living individual who is using our Service and is the subject of Personal Data.
Information Collection And Use
We collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Service to you.
Types of Data Collected
Personal Data
While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you (“Personal Data”). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:
Email address First name and last name Phone number Address, State, Province, ZIP/Postal code, City
Cookies and Usage Data
We may use your Personal Data to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send or by contacting us.
Usage Data
We may also collect information how the Service is accessed and used (“Usage Data”). This Usage Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.
Tracking & Cookies Data
We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and hold certain information.
Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service.
You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.
Examples of Cookies we use:
Session Cookies. We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.
Preference Cookies. We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.
Security Cookies. We use Security Cookies for security purposes.
Advertising Cookies. Advertising Cookies are used to serve you with advertisements that may be relevant to you and your interests.
Use of Personal Information
TradeWins Publishing will not rent, sell, or share your Personal Information to any unrelated third party except as described below. TradeWins Publishing may use your Personal Information for the following purposes:
To verify your user status, including without limitation by confirming that you are a TradeWins Publishing subscriber, that you have paid for particular content that requires payment or that you satisfy other conditions concerning particular content (e.g., geographic or time restrictions);
To process your transactions, including without limitation for billing purposes;
To confirm your subscription to or cancellation from TradeWins Publishing, or any particular purchases or licenses;
To improve our services;
To update and inform you about TradeWins Publishing services and products;
To send you offers from third party advertisers which are relevant and similar to our own
We provide Personal Information to trusted business partners that work on behalf of or with TradeWins Publishing under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your Personal Information to help TradeWins Publishing communicate with you about offers from TradeWins Publishing. Our business partners will be required to use any Personal Information we provide them only for that purpose.
Opt Out
If you do not wish to receive offers or other communications from us, you can opt-out by emailing customer service at adrienne@tradewins.com or by using the opt-out link that appears in our email correspondence. You can also edit your TradeWins Publishing Account Information, including your marketing preferences, at any time and may opt out of receiving promotional email communications in that fashion. You also have the ability to cancel or delete your TradeWins Publishing account by contacting our customer service. But after deleting your account, you will not have access to TradeWins Publishing features that require payment unless you re-subscribe. We reserve the right to send you announcements relating to TradeWins Publishing site or services, which may contain important information about the site or service, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them.
Legal Basis for Processing Personal Data Under General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)
If you are from the European Economic Area (EEA), TradeWins legal basis for collecting and using the personal information described in this Privacy Policy depends on the Personal Data we collect and the specific context in which we collect it.
Retention of Data
TradeWins will retain your Personal Data only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use your Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your data to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce our legal agreements and policies.
TradeWins will also retain Usage Data for internal analysis purposes. Usage Data is generally retained for a shorter period of time, except when this data is used to strengthen the security or to improve the functionality of our Service, or we are legally obligated to retain this data for longer time periods.
Transfer Of Data
Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.
If you are located outside United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to United States and process it there.
Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.
TradeWins will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.
Disclosures Required by Law and Investigations
We reserve the right to disclose your Personal Information in order to comply with any subpoenas, court orders or other legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.
We reserve the right to use and disclose your Personal Information in order to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, infringement of the intellectual property of TradeWins Publishing or a third party, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person or violations of TradeWins Publishing's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.
Security and Confidentiality of Personal Information
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure the correct use of Personal Information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures which we regard as appropriate to safeguard and secure the Personal Information we collect online.
We use encryption technology to protect the security of the information collected and transmitted on our website. When our registration and order forms ask users to enter sensitive Personal Information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software currently available in the industry, which is known as SSL.
In addition, your TradeWins Publishing Account Information is password-protected for your protection. After a successful login, you can change your password at your discretion. TradeWins Publishing recommends that you choose a password that would be difficult to guess, that you change your password periodically and that you keep your password secret (including by not allowing friends or family members to use your account and password). You acknowledge that you are responsible for selecting a password and maintaining its secrecy. Under no circumstances will TradeWins Publishing be liable to you or any third party for your failure to maintain the secrecy of your password.
No Liability for Acts of Third Parties
Although we will use reasonable efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of the Personal Information you submit, transmissions made by means of the Internet cannot be made absolutely secure. TradeWins Publishing will have no liability for disclosure of information and data you submit to us due to errors in transmission, unauthorized acts of third parties or through the use of third party cookies, programs, routines, viruses or other devices on your computer.
Once you leave the TradeWins Publishing site, including by clicking on links on our site, you will be subject to the privacy policies of third party website operators and other companies which may differ significantly from this policy. We encourage you to be aware of when you leave the TradeWins Publishing site and to read the privacy policies of each website that collects information from or about you.
Children
In order to register for the TradeWins Publishing Service, you must be at least 18 years of age. No information may be submitted to us by persons under the age of 13 without the consent of a parent or legal guardian, nor may persons under the age of 13 undertake transactions or take other legal acts on this site without such consent, unless permitted by applicable law.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
TradeWins Publishing may update this policy from time to time. We reserve the right to notify you about changes in the way we treat Personal Information by sending a notice to one or more of the email addresses specified in your TradeWins Publishing account or by placing a notice on the TradeWins Publishing site in a manner and for a period of time that we determine in our sole discretion.
Your Data Protection Rights Under General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)
If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), you have certain data protection rights. TradeWins aims to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your Personal Data.
If you wish to be informed what Personal Data we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us.
In certain circumstances, you have the following data protection rights:
The right to access, update or to delete the information we have on you. Whenever made possible, you can access, update or request deletion of your Personal Data directly within your account settings section. If you are unable to perform these actions yourself, please contact us to assist you.
The right of rectification. You have the right to have your information rectified if that information is inaccurate or incomplete.
The right to object. You have the right to object to our processing of your Personal Data.
The right of restriction. You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal information.
The right to data portability. You have the right to be provided with a copy of the information we have on you in a structured, machine-readable and commonly used format.
The right to withdraw consent. You also have the right to withdraw your consent at any time where TradeWins relied on your consent to process your personal information.
Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests.
You have the right to complain to a Data Protection Authority about our collection and use of your Personal Data. For more information, please contact your local data protection authority in the European Economic Area (EEA).
Service Providers
We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service (“Service Providers”), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.
These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.
Analytics
We may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service.
Payments
We may provide paid products and/or services within the Service. In that case, we use third-party services for payment processing (e.g. payment processors).
We will not store or collect your payment card details. That information is provided directly to our third-party payment processors whose use of your personal information is governed by their Privacy Policy. These payment processors adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, Mastercard, American Express and Discover. PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of payment information.
The payment processors we work with are:
Authorize.net
Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at https://www.authorize.net/company/privacy/
Links To Other Sites
Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.
We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us:
By email: kim@tradewins.com By visiting this page on our website: http://tradewins.com/privacy-policy By phone number: 888-233-1431 By mail: 22C New Leicester Highway #117, Asheville, NC 28806 United States
Home
Site Map
Government Required Disclaimer
Terms and Conditions
Trading Strategy
Webinars
Privacy Policy
Contact Us
